(Leonard:)Wait. So we just go over there?
(Howard:)No. We have a little prep work to do.
(Howard:)Put this in your mouth, we walk past them,
you stumble a bit.
I say, "Sorry,
my friend's had a little too much."
(Howard:)And then I start to pull it
out of your mouth and say:
"A little too much fun."
[LAUGHS]
(Howard:)Get it? I mean, they're laughing,
we're laughing. Then we get them up...
...to about a 0.15 blood alcohol level
and tell them we're millionaires.
(Leonard:)What else you got?
(Howard:)Depends. Are you willing to sit on my lap
and pretend to be a ventriloquist's dummy?
(Penny:)No.
(Howard:)I can't sit on your lap.
You don't know the routine.
(Stuart:)I'm sorry, but you're obviously stuck
in a pre-Zero Hour DC Universe.
(Sheldon:)Of course I am. Removing Joe Chill
as the killer of Batman's parents...
(Sheldon:)...effectively deprived him
of his raison d'être.
(Stuart:)You can throw all the French around
you want, it doesn't make you right.
(Sheldon:)Au contraire.